[
  {
    "question": "We had one problem__ only Janet knew we faced bankruptcy.",
    "options": {
      "a": ":",
      "b": ",",
      "c": ";",
      "d": "."
    },
    "correct": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Wales__",
    "options": {
      "a": ".",
      "b": "!",
      "c": "?",
      "d": "□"
    },
    "correct": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "What a lovely view you have here__",
    "options": {
      "a": "!",
      "b": ".",
      "c": "□",
      "d": "?"
    },
    "correct": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "She asked if I had a pen she could borrow__",
    "options": {
      "a": "?",
      "b": ".",
      "c": "!",
      "d": ":"
    },
    "correct": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Norway has applied for EC membership__ Sweden is expected to do the same.",
    "options": {
      "a": ",",
      "b": ".",
      "c": ";",
      "d": ":"
    },
    "correct": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lisa speaks French, Juliet speaks Italian __ I speak Spanish.",
    "options": {
      "a": "and",
      "b": ",",
      "c": ";",
      "d": "but"
    },
    "correct": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stanley was a determined__ even ruthless__ figure.",
    "options": {
      "a": ", ,",
      "b": ": :",
      "c": "; ;",
      "d": "□ □"
    },
    "correct": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Italy is famous for her composers and musicians__ France, for her chefs.",
    "options": {
      "a": ",",
      "b": ":",
      "c": ";",
      "d": ""
    },
    "correct": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lisa is upset__ Gus is having a nervous breakdown.",
    "options": {
      "a": ".",
      "b": ";",
      "c": ",",
      "d": ":"
    },
    "correct": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "She was sure of one thing__ she was not going to be a housewife.",
    "options": {
      "a": ":",
      "b": ",",
      "c": ";",
      "d": "."
    },
    "correct": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "The girls__ room was painted bright pink.",
    "options": {
      "a": "'",
      "b": "’",
      "c": "□",
      "d": "’s"
    },
    "correct": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "She can't go to the party because she's got the flu__",
    "options": {
      "a": ".",
      "b": "!",
      "c": "?",
      "d": ","
    },
    "correct": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "He said__ 'I will not do it!'",
    "options": {
      "a": ":",
      "b": ",",
      "c": ";",
      "d": "."
    },
    "correct": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "The results were disappointing__ the project was shut down.",
    "options": {
      "a": ",",
      "b": ":",
      "c": ";",
      "d": "."
    },
    "correct": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "After months of work, the scientists opened the tomb__ it was empty!",
    "options": {
      "a": ".",
      "b": ";",
      "c": ":",
      "d": ","
    },
    "correct": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mind your p__s and q__s.",
    "options": {
      "a": "'",
      "b": "’",
      "c": "□",
      "d": ","
    },
    "correct": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "One must choose one__s words carefully.",
    "options": {
      "a": "'",
      "b": ",",
      "c": "’",
      "d": "□"
    },
    "correct": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "The publication of The Hobbit in 1937__ marked the beginning of Tolkien’s career.",
    "options": {
      "a": ",",
      "b": ".",
      "c": ":",
      "d": ";"
    },
    "correct": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Note that__ in each of these examples, the material could be removed.",
    "options": {
      "a": ",",
      "b": ":",
      "c": ";",
      "d": "."
    },
    "correct": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Josie wanted to be a teacher__ but after university she became a lawyer.",
    "options": {
      "a": ",",
      "b": ";",
      "c": ".",
      "d": ":"
    },
    "correct": "a"
  }
]
